# Jessa Design

# **WEBSITE / PORTFOLIO**

jessadesign.com

## **SKILLS & PROFICIENCY**

HTML/CSS

Javascript/jQuery

PHP

**SEO** 

WordPress/CMS

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe InDesign

Dreamweaver/Sublime

Other Proficiencies: FileZilla, cPanel, Bootstrap, Microsoft Office, eCommerce, Graphic Design, Xampp, Multi-Tasking, Attention to Detail, Verbal and Written Communication

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **University of Wisconsin - Madison**

Bachelor of Science (Web Design) Graduated 2015

# **REFERENCES**

Available upon request.

# JESSA VANDERPOEL

jessa.vanderpoel@gmail.com · (312) 615 6771 · Palatine, IL

## **PROFILE**

Highly-motivated front-end web developer with over four years experience designing and maintaining professional websites. Successfully implemented responsive, mobile-first sites with attention to SEO standards. Quick learner and adept problem-solver. Excellent communication skills with an ability to describe technical information in easy-to-understand terms. Eager to grow professionally.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## Front-End Web Developer and SEO Specialist

WebHostingPad.com, Inc. | Arlington Heights, IL (October 2016 - Present)

- Redeveloped multiple websites to be fully responsive and in-line with modern web design standards and practices.
- Developed js/jQuery scripts for: navigational menus, collapsible tables, form validation, pop ups, tooltips, quick search.
- Edited site structure and content to be SEO-friendly for chosen keywords.
- Collaborated with other developers, designers, SEO specialists, and translators to complete various website implementations and features.
- Other tasks including: responding to customer complaints and reviews, coordinating with international marketing personnel, creating and sending promotional materials such as newsletters, social media posts, and digital ads.

## **Freelance Graphic Designer**

Jessa Design | Illinois & Wisconsin (August 2015 - October 2016)

• Designed various graphic design materials including company logos, menus, flyers, brochures, and PDFs to clients' specifications and modern design standards.

#### Front-of-House Team Member

Ian's Pizza on State | Madison, WI (June 2014 - June 2015)

- Cashiered, bussed tables, took orders, restocked, and performed other basic front-of-house duties in a fast-paced and busy environment with frequent rushes.
- Memorized ingredients to quickly and correctly answer customer questions and make recommendations based on dietary restrictions and personal preferences.
- Adhered to high standards for customer service and satisfaction.

## **Dining & Culinary Team Member**

University of Wisconsin Housing | Madison, WI (September 2011 - June 2014)

- Prepared and served customer orders, assisted back-of-house chefs with cooking and cleaning, cashiered, bussed tables, and other related tasks.
- Worked on the delivery team to take orders, prepare food for traveling, and deliver multiple orders to customers efficiently and within quoted delivery times.